<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Genevieve&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blogletters/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Genevieve&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>genevieve@grand_archive.abs (Genevieve Cayley)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>genevieve@grand_archive.abs (Genevieve Cayley)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blogletters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Invitation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogletters/journal/greetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>genevieve@grand_archive.abs (Genevieve Cayley)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogletters/journal/greetings/</guid>
      <description>It seems I&amp;#39;ve been invited to Lord Kiordan&amp;#39;s Grand Masquerade, for mysterious and of course undisclosed reasons. I was briefly tempted to refuse, but this is hardly an opportunity one can pass up. And besides, it has been a long time since I last passed through Geb. Too long, perhaps.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It seems I&#39;ve been invited to Lord Kiordan&#39;s Grand Masquerade, for mysterious and of course undisclosed reasons. I was briefly tempted to refuse, but this is hardly an opportunity one can pass up. And besides, it has been a long time since I last passed through Geb. Too long, perhaps.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogletters/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>genevieve@grand_archive.abs (Genevieve Cayley)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogletters/about/</guid>
      <description>Genevieve Cayley Biography Traveled the world extensively as a scholar, developed a fascination with mental/psionic magic Settled down in Absalom as an enigmatic academic Wound up working with the Grand Archive, trained in being a psychic Her recent work - some fairly technical but still fascinating research on mental hardening - methods to secure the mind against control and possession Appearance Height: 3&#39;6, tall for a gnome but short for everything else Eyes: Piercing electric blue Hair: Pixie cut, color changes every day but it&amp;rsquo;s usually something vibrant and noticeable Hands casting somatic message as a stim Eyes always staring intently at a target as if boring a hole in them Very rarely blinks </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 id="genevieve-cayley">Genevieve Cayley</h1>
<h2 id="biography">Biography</h2>
<ul>
<li>Traveled the world extensively as a scholar, developed a fascination with mental/psionic magic</li>
<li>Settled down in Absalom as an enigmatic academic</li>
<li>Wound up working with the Grand Archive, trained in being a psychic</li>
<li>Her recent work - some fairly technical but still fascinating research on mental hardening - methods to secure the mind against control and possession</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="appearance">Appearance</h2>
<ul>
<li>Height: 3'6, tall for a gnome but short for everything else</li>
<li>Eyes: Piercing electric blue</li>
<li>Hair: Pixie cut, color changes every day but it&rsquo;s usually something vibrant and noticeable</li>
<li>Hands casting somatic <em>message</em> as a stim</li>
<li>Eyes always staring intently at a target as if boring a hole in them</li>
<li>Very rarely blinks</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
